<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://anoncoin.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://anoncoin.net/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-08-05T09:40:18+02:00</updated><id>https://anoncoin.net/</id><title type="html">Anoncoin</title><subtitle>Anoncoin(ANC) is a unique decentralized peer to peer internet cryptocurrency that provides for its users. I2P and Tor compatible, it is resistant to crackdowns from hostile authorities.  </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Anoncoin 0.9.7 release with hardfork</title><link href="https://anoncoin.net/update/2018/07/13/Anoncoin-0_9_7/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Anoncoin 0.9.7 release with hardfork" /><published>2018-07-13T13:14:35+02:00</published><updated>2018-07-13T13:14:35+02:00</updated><id>https://anoncoin.net/update/2018/07/13/Anoncoin-0_9_7</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anoncoin.net/update/2018/07/13/Anoncoin-0_9_7/">&lt;p&gt;The Anoncoin team is proud to announce the official release of Anoncoin 0.9.7. This release is set to hardfork at block 871111, giving everyone about 1 week to upgrade. This is a first step on the way for the release of Anoncash later this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will release builds out for all platforms which makes it easy for new users to install and run Anoncoin. You can &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Anoncoin/anoncoin/releases/tag/v0.9.7-gost&quot;&gt;find the release on Github here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;gost-r-3411-2012&quot;&gt;GOST R 34.11-2012&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We fixed issues with some mined blocks not being accepted, and in the process we moved to double GOST R 34.11-2012 hashing algorithm, mined with CPU/GPU. Now everyone in the Anoncoin community can mine, rather than those few who have an ASIC miner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hardfork-at-block-871111&quot;&gt;Hardfork at block 871111.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To move over to GOST R 34.11-2012 a hardfork is needed. This will happen at block 871111, in about 1 week from now. Please make sure you have upgraded by that time. Any blocks mined from miners that have not upgraded will not be accepted after this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recommend that you upgrade your wallet before making transactions. The two largest Anoncoin exchanges, &lt;a href=&quot;https://freiexchange.com&quot;&gt;FreiExchange.com&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://miraiex.com&quot;&gt;MiraiEx.com&lt;/a&gt; will upgrade, there is no need to move your coins before the hardfork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;contributors&quot;&gt;Contributors.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anoncoin is an open source project and depends on volunteers contributing their time and effort to the project. Important contributors for development and testing of this release is Meeh, Oyvkva, JSX, Orignal and Killertaco. Thanks to the rest of our community for support as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bit.ly/2NEVapT&quot;&gt;Join us at Slack by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Anoncoin team is proud to announce the official release of Anoncoin 0.9.7. This release is set to hardfork at block 871111, giving everyone about 1 week to upgrade. This is a first step on the way for the release of Anoncash later this year.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bitcointalk announcement October 22, 2017</title><link href="https://anoncoin.net/update/2017/10/22/Bitcointalk-announcement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bitcointalk announcement October 22, 2017" /><published>2017-10-22T13:14:35+02:00</published><updated>2017-10-22T13:14:35+02:00</updated><id>https://anoncoin.net/update/2017/10/22/Bitcointalk-announcement</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anoncoin.net/update/2017/10/22/Bitcointalk-announcement/">&lt;p&gt;We are posting this here as well, but it can be found on &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=227287.msg23383240#msg23383240&quot;&gt;Bitcoin talk here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a short announcement on behalf of me, Meeh and a couple of friends who would like to work on the AnonCoin project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TLDR;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeh and some other developers have started active development on Anoncoin. A new release expected in December. We have a Slack, &lt;a href=&quot;https://join.slack.com/t/anoncoin/shared_invite/enQtMjcxMzUxMjk5ODYwLTU0OTJhNmIxNzYyY2JiMzUxOGZhMjYzNmQ3YmViNWM1OWIxZGNlMGY0Zjg1NzdhMDAyZmRiYTFhNTM1OWZiYTU&quot;&gt;talk with us here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;Intro.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeh started the project years ago, I’ve been around and following crypto for a few years. We’ve been talking about it for a while, but recently we decided to get together with a few more developers to work on Anoncoin again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blockchain is running, people are mining, but there has not been any activity on the git repo since June 19. After the delisting on BTC38 trading volume has been very low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;community&quot;&gt;Community.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We would really like to revive the project and hope to see support from the community. There have been lots of people with valuable contributions over the years. Thanks to everyone, and especially the people who have kept the project alive for the last few years!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be active on both slack and IRC2P moving forwards. Hopefully, we can also manage to bring the Anoncoin Reddit back to life, it’s a good place for new people to learn about the project. A new website is also being worked on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of this is suggestions and ideas. We want to hear from everyone with an interest in Anoncoin what they would like to see. We really want to see this project succeed and believe there is a huge potential, especially at this time with Bitcoin making new ATHs over and over and media is writing about cryptocurrencies constantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;goals&quot;&gt;Goals.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the coming 2 months, we would like to update the current codebase. We are planning to use the Actor Framework. The actor model has advantages with simpler scalability and concurrency. The goal is to have a new release ready in December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 2018 we have big plans that we would like to discuss with the community. We would like a new codebase, possibly based on CryptoNote instead of ZeroCoin. We would also like a more egalitarian PoW mining algorithm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will write in more detail about development goals in a roadmap soon, but it would be really good to hear what people think first. &lt;a href=&quot;https://join.slack.com/t/anoncoin/shared_invite/enQtMjcxMzUxMjk5ODYwLTU0OTJhNmIxNzYyY2JiMzUxOGZhMjYzNmQ3YmViNWM1OWIxZGNlMGY0Zjg1NzdhMDAyZmRiYTFhNTM1OWZiYTU&quot;&gt;Talk with us on Slack here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are also at #anoncoin-dev on IRC2P.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We are posting this here as well, but it can be found on Bitcoin talk here.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Moving over to Jekyll</title><link href="https://anoncoin.net/update/2017/10/14/Moving-to-Jekyll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Moving over to Jekyll" /><published>2017-10-14T13:14:35+02:00</published><updated>2017-10-14T13:14:35+02:00</updated><id>https://anoncoin.net/update/2017/10/14/Moving-to-Jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anoncoin.net/update/2017/10/14/Moving-to-Jekyll/">&lt;p&gt;We decided to move the website over to Jekyll. Jekyll is a simple, blog-aware, static site generator. It takes a template directory containing raw text files in various formats, runs it through a converter (like Markdown) and the Liquid renderer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It then spits out a complete, ready-to-publish static website suitable for serving. Jekyll also happens to be the engine behind GitHub Pages, which makes it suitable for a project like Anoncoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using Jekyll it is easy for people to make changes to this website by making a pull request on Github. Project maintainers can then easily see what changes have been made and merge them into the main repository and update the website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We decided to move the website over to Jekyll. Jekyll is a simple, blog-aware, static site generator. It takes a template directory containing raw text files in various formats, runs it through a converter (like Markdown) and the Liquid renderer.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Updates</title><link href="https://anoncoin.net/update/2017/10/13/Updates/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Updates" /><published>2017-10-13T13:14:35+02:00</published><updated>2017-10-13T13:14:35+02:00</updated><id>https://anoncoin.net/update/2017/10/13/Updates</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anoncoin.net/update/2017/10/13/Updates/">&lt;p&gt;Not much have happened with Anoncoin the last couple of years. We would like to change that and are planning a lot of exciting updates in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before Christmas we want to have a new release out with working builds for all major platforms. We are also working on a mobile wallet for iOS and Android that will be done any time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Not much have happened with Anoncoin the last couple of years. We would like to change that and are planning a lot of exciting updates in the coming months.</summary></entry></feed>